<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Sermons on Adam Brown's Cloud</title><link>https://adambrown.cloud/categories/sermons/</link><description>Recent content in Sermons on Adam Brown's Cloud</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2025 10:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://adambrown.cloud/categories/sermons/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Your Kingdom Come, Your Will Be Done</title><link>https://adambrown.cloud/posts/sermon-notes-25-may/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://adambrown.cloud/posts/sermon-notes-25-may/</guid><description>&lt;p>This is the second post in the &lt;strong>sermon notes series on the Lord’s Prayer&lt;/strong>, and I found this one to be particularly interesting and somewhat thought-provoking. As always, these are just simple reflections and takeaways from the Sunday messages at &lt;a href="https://standrewsbangor.org.uk" target="_blank" rel="noopener">St Andrew’s Presbyterian Church, Bangor&lt;/a>. I hope they’ll be an encouragement and a way for me to think aloud as I follow Jesus.&lt;/p>
&lt;h1 id="your-kingdom-come-your-will-be-done-learning-to-submit-like-jesus">Your Kingdom Come, Your Will Be Done: Learning to Submit Like Jesus&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>As we continue our journey through &lt;strong>Luke 11:1–4&lt;/strong>, the focus shifts to the second and third petitions of the Lord’s Prayer: &lt;em>&amp;ldquo;Your kingdom come. Your will be done, on earth as it is in heaven.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em> These are not just words of hope&amp;ndash;they are words of surrender.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Sermon Notes - 18 May - Hallowed be your Name</title><link>https://adambrown.cloud/posts/sermon-notes-18-may/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://adambrown.cloud/posts/sermon-notes-18-may/</guid><description>&lt;p>Faith is an important part of my life, and at its core, trying to understand how things plug together is another key part of what makes me &lt;em>me&lt;/em>. As part of that, I&amp;rsquo;ll be sharing sermon notes here from time to time&amp;ndash;simple reflections and takeaways from the Sunday messages at &lt;a href="https://standrewsbangor.org.uk" target="_blank" rel="noopener">St Andrew&amp;rsquo;s Presbyterian Church, Bangor&lt;/a>. I hope they&amp;rsquo;ll be an encouragement and a way for me to think aloud as I follow Jesus.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>