<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dyspraxia on Adam Brown&#39;s Cloud</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/dyspraxia/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dyspraxia on Adam Brown&#39;s Cloud</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 10:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/dyspraxia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
      <title>What Remote Work Reveals About Inclusion for Neurodivergent People</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/inclusive-remote-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/inclusive-remote-work/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;On a recent holiday, I finally had the space to slow down and process—a rare luxury in the rhythm of modern work.&lt;/strong&gt; While recharging (easier said than done, for me at least!), I was reflecting on what remote work really means for neurodivergent people like me. I’m autistic and dyspraxic, and full-time remote work has been transformative in many ways. It removes the sensory overwhelm of office spaces, reduces social masking, and gives me more control over my environment. But it also made one thing clear: the issue was never just &lt;em&gt;where&lt;/em&gt; we work—it’s &lt;em&gt;how&lt;/em&gt; we work, and who the systems are built for.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Beginnings</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/new-beginnings/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 08:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/new-beginnings/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi there - I&amp;rsquo;m glad you&amp;rsquo;ve found your way here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m Adam, and this blog exists for a reason that&amp;rsquo;s both personal and practical. I live with photosensitive epilepsy and dyspraxia. These conditions shape how I experience the world — sometimes in challenging ways, but often in ways that have given me unique perspectives, habits, and ways of working.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Professionally, I&amp;rsquo;ve built a career in technical consulting. I thrive in environments where I can solve complex problems, build systems that work for people, and translate technical detail into something meaningful. But it hasn&amp;rsquo;t always been easy to balance that with my own health needs. The truth is, living and working with invisible disabilities often means constantly negotiating boundaries, managing overstimulation, and finding workarounds that aren&amp;rsquo;t visible to others.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
