<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Faith on Adam Brown's Cloud</title><link>https://adambrown.cloud/tags/faith/</link><description>Recent content in Faith on Adam Brown's Cloud</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 10:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://adambrown.cloud/tags/faith/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Sermon Notes - 8 June - Forgive Everyone for Everything</title><link>https://adambrown.cloud/posts/seemon-notes-8-june/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://adambrown.cloud/posts/seemon-notes-8-june/</guid><description>&lt;p>Faith is central to my life, but it&amp;rsquo;s also in the small things&amp;ndash;how we speak, how we pray, and especially how we respond when we’ve been wronged. This week at &lt;a href="https://standrewsbangor.org.uk" target="_blank" rel="noopener">St Andrew’s Presbyterian Church, Bangor&lt;/a>, we continued our series through the Lord’s Prayer, focusing on a challenging but essential line:&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>&lt;em>&amp;ldquo;Forgive us our sins, for we also forgive everyone who sins against us.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em>&lt;br>
&amp;ndash; &lt;strong>Luke 11:4 (NIV)&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;p>Jesus’ teaching on forgiveness is never abstract. It&amp;rsquo;s practical, relational, and deeply personal. Forgiveness is not just something we receive; it&amp;rsquo;s something we extend.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Sermon Notes - 1 June - Give Us Each Day Our Daily Bread</title><link>https://adambrown.cloud/posts/sermon-notes-1-june/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2025 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://adambrown.cloud/posts/sermon-notes-1-june/</guid><description>&lt;p>Faith is an important part of my life, and at its core, trying to understand how things plug together is another key part of what makes me &lt;em>me&lt;/em>. Over the past few weeks, I’ve been sharing sermon notes from our current series at &lt;a href="https://standrewsbangor.org.uk" target="_blank" rel="noopener">St Andrew&amp;rsquo;s Presbyterian Church, Bangor&lt;/a>, where we’ve been walking slowly through the Lord’s Prayer in Luke’s Gospel.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This post follows on from the previous reflections on &lt;em>&amp;ldquo;Father, hallowed be your name&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em> and &lt;em>&amp;ldquo;Your kingdom come,&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em> turning now to the next petition: &lt;em>&amp;ldquo;Give us each day our daily bread.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em> A short and familiar phrase, yet full of meaning&amp;ndash;an invitation to live with dependence, humility, and trust in God’s faithful provision.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Your Kingdom Come, Your Will Be Done</title><link>https://adambrown.cloud/posts/sermon-notes-25-may/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://adambrown.cloud/posts/sermon-notes-25-may/</guid><description>&lt;p>This is the second post in the &lt;strong>sermon notes series on the Lord’s Prayer&lt;/strong>, and I found this one to be particularly interesting and somewhat thought-provoking. As always, these are just simple reflections and takeaways from the Sunday messages at &lt;a href="https://standrewsbangor.org.uk" target="_blank" rel="noopener">St Andrew’s Presbyterian Church, Bangor&lt;/a>. I hope they’ll be an encouragement and a way for me to think aloud as I follow Jesus.&lt;/p>
&lt;h1 id="your-kingdom-come-your-will-be-done-learning-to-submit-like-jesus">Your Kingdom Come, Your Will Be Done: Learning to Submit Like Jesus&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>As we continue our journey through &lt;strong>Luke 11:1–4&lt;/strong>, the focus shifts to the second and third petitions of the Lord’s Prayer: &lt;em>&amp;ldquo;Your kingdom come. Your will be done, on earth as it is in heaven.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em> These are not just words of hope&amp;ndash;they are words of surrender.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Sermon Notes - 18 May - Hallowed be your Name</title><link>https://adambrown.cloud/posts/sermon-notes-18-may/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://adambrown.cloud/posts/sermon-notes-18-may/</guid><description>&lt;p>Faith is an important part of my life, and at its core, trying to understand how things plug together is another key part of what makes me &lt;em>me&lt;/em>. As part of that, I&amp;rsquo;ll be sharing sermon notes here from time to time&amp;ndash;simple reflections and takeaways from the Sunday messages at &lt;a href="https://standrewsbangor.org.uk" target="_blank" rel="noopener">St Andrew&amp;rsquo;s Presbyterian Church, Bangor&lt;/a>. I hope they&amp;rsquo;ll be an encouragement and a way for me to think aloud as I follow Jesus.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>